Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology. Research Office records, 1947-2007
New York State College of Human Ecology. Research Office records, 1947-2007
- Series VIII. Faculty Research Reports
  - Pillemer, Karl - Aging and Family Relations, HDFS, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Pillemer, Karl and Moen, Phyllis - Cornell Applied Gerontology Research Institute, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Pollak, Patricia- Removing Regulatory Barriers to Housing Innovations for the Elderly, CEH, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Potts, Marion - Childrearing Practices of Rural Families, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Putsis, William - A Simultaneous Equaton Approach to the Cooley-Prescott Model of Time-Varying Parameters, CEH, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Raver, C. Cybele - Effective Parenting Practices and the Resilient Social Competence of Low-Income Preschoolers, HDFS, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Raver, C. Cybele - Reciprocity and Conflict in the Intersections of Low-Income Mothers and Their Children, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Reeves, Terrie - Factors That Influence Health Services Organizational Change, PAM, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Ricciuti, Henry - Development of At-Risk Children in Rural Poor Families, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Robertson, Stephen S. - Spontaneous Activity of the Fetus and Infant, HDFS, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Rodriguez, Eunice - A Comparative Analysis of the Role of Social Support in Buffering the Impact of Unemployment on Health, HSS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Saltford, Nancy and Heck, Ramona - Employee Benefits for Working Families in Nonmetropolitan Areas, HDFS, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Savin-Williams, Ritch - Peer Teasing and Ridicule Among Adolescents, HDFS, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Salvin-Williams, Ritch - A Longitudinal Study Assessing Urban Sexual Minority Adolescents for HIV, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Schoggen, Phil - Adolescent Participation in Community Behavioral Settings, HDFS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Schoggen, Phil - The Children of New York: Early Childhood Development and Education in. New York State Project 2000, HDFS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Schwartz, Peter - Interfaces in Composite Materials, TXA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Schwartz, Peter - Correlation of Multiple Failure Mechanisms in Monofilaments, TXA, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Schwartz, Peter and Obendorf, S. Kay - Mapping of Noncrystalline Regions in Polymers, TXA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Street, Llyod - Race, Crime, and Community, HSS, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Suci, George - Processing Visual Events and Language by Infants, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Thorton, Michael - Patterns of Ethnic Minority Identity, HDFS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Trochim, William, and Greene, Jennifer - Kelly Research Evaluation Conference, 1992-1997, HSS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Watkins, Susan - Concepts Development for Next Generation/Future Systems for Clothing and Individual Equipment, TXA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Watkins, Susan and Ashdown, Susan - Analysis, Design, and Testing of Protective Coveralls Worn by Asbestos Abatement Crews, TXA, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Wethington, Elaine - Neighboring in Life Course Perspective, HDFS, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Wethington, Elaine - Employment, Family, and Psychological Distress: Processes of Role Stress and Stress Spillover, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Ziegert, Beate - Apparel Design/Stretch Fabric Interaction Applied to Computer Design Technology, TXA, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 82)